Contact

hectddos103@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/hectorrodrigues-da-silva-4073b3191 (LinkedIn)

Main competencies

React.js

TypeScript

Next.js

Certifications

Alura | Web Developer Introduction to Computer Science

Discover

Hector Rodrigues da Silva

Front-end Enginner at FullCam & Founder Mexpenses Garça, São Paulo, Brazil

Resume

Programming since was 16 years old and currently 21 years, have technical english and almost 5 years of professional experience in web programming, I am always looking to learn, improve and learn about new technologies on the current market, so that I can apply this knowledge aiming for a stable architecture and excellent quality in your services.

Experiences

Fulltime - Soluções e Tecnologias de Monitoramento e Rastreamento

4 years 8 months

Front-end Enginner at FullCam Octuber 2020 - Present (3 year 6 months) Garça, São Paulo, Brazil

- Architetures
- Refactors
- Landing Pages
- New features
- Bug fixes
- Code review
- Deploy

Leading a Front-end development team with experience in a product that manages Live images, Recordings and Events through our easy-to-use timelines, where it is possible have endless possibilities to make security more flexible in end-to-end monitoring in a given region. Which in turn covers other features through our AI (Artificial Intelligence) for Detecting people, Animals, Vehicles, License Plate Reading, delimiting the detection/Collision area and much more. The FullCam product continues with the same technology

cutting-edge, but with the difference of being 100% customizable, from the appearance of the platform to the storage location.

More information: https://fullcam.me

Trainee Front-end Engineer at FullCam August 2019 - Octuber 2020 (1 year 3 months) Garça, Brazil.

Mexpenses

Founder

January 2021 - Present (3 years 3 months)

Garça, São Paulo, Brazil

- AWS
- Architetures
- Payments
- Refactors
- Landing Pages
- New features
- Bug fixes
- Code review
- Deploy

Founder and developer of software that provides practical and simple solutions for personal financial management. Its main function is to help users save and deal with their debts and investments for free or through subscriptions with benefits.

More information: https://www.mexpenses.net

Academic education

Fatec Garça - Deputado Julio Julinho Marcondes de Moura Technologist, Analysis and Systems Development · (February 2021 – February 2022)

Etec Garça - Monsenhor Antônio Magliano
Technical, Systems Development, Information Technology · (July 2018 – December 2019)